Max 二号桌的小费你拿了吗?
Max, did you pick up the tip from table two?
没 但我确定自己得了葡萄球菌
No, but I'm pretty sure I picked up a staph infection.
他们真的是一毛不拔
So they literally gave me their two cents worth.
这太让人尴尬了
This is so embarrassing,
连钱上的林肯都不忍直视
even Abe Lincoln won't make eye contact.
姑娘们 你们得帮我做件事
Girls, I need you to do something for me.
规矩你懂 你那里 你身上 你身边
You know the rule: nothing for you,
或者我们身体里 都不能有东西
on you, near you, or in us.
我要去上厕所 你们看着厨房
I'm going to restroom. Keep eye on the kitchen.
我煮的蛋还有四分钟 我还和运动画刊泳装特辑
I have a four-minute egg and a five-minute date
有个五分钟的约会
with the Sports Illustrated Swimsuit Issue.
嘿 你看到我看到的了吗?
Hey, do you see what I see?
着火了?
A fire?
不是 是摆脱这工作的方法
No, a way out of this job.
我的天啊 着火了
Lord Jesus, there's a fire.
你们两个打算去处理吗?
You two gonna do anything about that?
我反正不会去
'Cause I'm not.
我可不敢玩火 还有惹长老教会的人
I don't mess with fire or Presbyterians.
着火了 着火了!
Fire, fire!
我闻到火了!
I smell fire!
别光站着啊 做点事!
Well, don't just stand there. Do something!
我们在干事啊
We are.
做饼干!
S'mores!
你觉得这地方被烧没了你会很开心吗
You'd think you want this place to burn to the ground.
你这么觉得吧
You'd think that.
Caroline 干点事啊
Caroline, do something.
好的 要巧克力吗?
I'm on it. Chocolate?
Han 别靠太近了
Han, not too close.
衣服沾上的韩式烧烤的味儿
You know you can never get the smell of Korean barbecue
可是永远挥之不去的
out of your clothes.
他要么是在灭火
Either he put the fire out,
要么就是这小机器人高潮了
or that little robot just had an orgasm.
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组  http://hdscg.com/ ==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 。沫
翻译: 再小黄就去面壁的小黄  波特妹子  Morning  奥利奥
校对: 桃茜茜
欢迎来到糕潮甜品吧
Welcome to The High dessert bar.
我是迎宾员兼准经理
I'm the hostess slash quasi-manager.
我第一天来就升职了
First day in, got a huge promosh.
我不想炫耀
I hate to brag,
但有人说我非常耀眼
but the word dezzaling was used.
是啊 你自己说的
Yeah, by you.
小小权利就让你冲昏了头
Little to no power has really gone to your head.
就是
It has.
她就像是糕点界的普京
She's like the Putin of pastry.
不在餐馆打工的这种感觉
But doesn't it feel good
难道不好吗
to not just be working at the diner?
我一整天都没有踩到用过的婴儿尿布
I haven't slipped on one used baby diaper all day.
说到婴儿
Speaking of babies,
看 Han来了
look, there's Han.
这已经是我第三次
That's, like, the third time
看到他在偷窥我们了
I caught him spying on us.
他干嘛要跟踪他最差的两个雇员啊?
Why would he stalk two of his worst employees?
就是啊
I know.
就像"沃利藏在哪了"这动画
It's like Where's Waldo
可是你都不想找到沃利啊
when you don't want to find Waldo.
怎么没有见到迎宾小姐
Not seeing a hostess up in here.
她想说的是准经理
She meant quasi-manager.
要是马丁·斯科塞斯走进来
If Marty Scorsese walks in here,
你想让他自己找地方坐吗?
do you want him to seat himself?
他会迷路的 迷路
He'll be lost. Lost.
不好意思 Joe 我只是在那边给Max..
Sorry, Joe, I was just over there giving Max...
亲爱的 我如果想要听故事的话
Honey, I'll download an audiobook
会自己去下载有声书刊的
if I want to hear a story.
有个人我想介绍给你
I want you to meet someone.
我也想见 只要时机合适
Me too, and I'm sure I will when the time is right
而且我愿意接纳别人
and I'm open to it.
现在还是专注于自己的事比较好
Kind of focusing on me right now.
停
Stop.
学会读懂表情
Learn to read faces.
我说的不是你
I'm not talking about you.
我是在说他
I'm talking about him.
你好 见到你很高兴
Hello, pleasure to meet you.
我是Nashit
I'm Nashit.
Nashit是一个印度的名字
Nashit's an Indian name,
然后我听到的是爱尔兰口音吧?
and isn't that an Irish accent I detect?
或者是你一口大白牙
Or have I just lost consciousness
把我闪得人都傻了?
from how white your teeth are?
是的
Yes, it is.
我爸爸是印度人 我妈妈是爱尔兰人
My father's Indian. My mother's Irish.
他是爱尔兰人 还是印度人
He's Irish. He's Indian.
他就是东方与西方的碰撞
He's East meets West.
他是一切
He's everything
热腾腾的爱尔兰咖啡 男孩乐队
in a hot Irish coffee, boy band package.
我在街上发现了他
I found him on the street
他就坐在一个脏乎乎的椅子旁边
next to a dirty chair.
你好 我是Caroline 是糕潮
Hi, I'm Caroline, the hostess slash quasi-manager
迎宾兼准经理
at The High.
你嗑药了吗?
Are you high?
你话真是多
'Cause that was a lot of talking.
这是谁啊 我怎么也搞一个来?
Who is this, and where can I get one?
他是Nashit 我们的新服务员
This is Nashit, our new waiter.
哦 见到你很高兴
Oh, it's lovely to meet you.
你能说"太好吃了"吗?
Can you say magically delicios?
我非常希望Nashit能成功
I really want Nashit to work out.
我喜欢看到漂亮的人成功
I like it when good-looking people succeed.
那这对我来说一定是好消息
Well, I guess that's good news for me.
是吗?
Is it?
嘿 亲爱的
Hi, honey.
你见过新的服务员了吗?
Have you met the new waiter?
我爱他 他是我的最爱
I love him. He's my favorite.
如果我要上男人 我肯定把他上了
If I did men, he would've been done by now.
嗯 你觉得你很好看对吧
Hmm, so you think you're pretty.
我也觉得
Well, I do too.
好吧 Nashit 注意听
Okay, Nashit, pay attention.
这些是桌子 这是甜点吧台
These are the tables. This is the dessert bar.
这是我的胸
And these are my boobs.
Max 专业点
Max, be professional.
这是我的胸 先生
These are my boobs, sir.
别这样 我还要教他做服务员呢
Please, I have to make him a waiter.
好吧 你教他做服务员
Fine, you make him a waiter,
我待会儿来做他这个服务员
and I'll just make him later.
给你 这不是你们的 对吧?
Here you go. This isn't yours, is it?
不是 因为他们已经吃过甜点了
No, because they already have dessert.
妈的
Damn it.
你一个小时之前就要水了 对吧?
You asked for water, like, an hour ago, didn't you?
太抱歉了
I'm so sorry.
哦 别担心我们的嘴唇会干
Oh, don't you worry those lips.
漫漫人生 等一个小时候又何妨?
And what's an hour when we have our whole lives ahead of us?
Max 我不知道该怎么办了
Max, I don't know what I'm gonna do.
我这个服务员太差劲了
I stink as a waiter.
这真是太难受了
This is desperate.
难受的时候需要亲热
Well, desperate times call for us making out.
嘿 我有个问题问你
Hey, I have a question for you.
你的皮肤如此光滑白皙
Your skin is so creamy and white.
你肯定有爱尔兰人血统吧
You must have a little Irish in you.
我体内有很多爱尔兰因子哦
I've had a lot of little Irishes in me.
这是挑逗的话吧?
That's meant to be dirty, right?
我只是想说我觉得你非常漂亮
Well, I just mean that I think you're quite beautiful.
好吧 我只是想说我们做定了
Oh, well, then I just mean we're doing it.
我以前觉得没人
I did not think there was somebody
有比我还漂亮的鼻子 或者做服务员
who had a prettier nose or was worse than me
比我还差 但你做到了
waiting tables, but here we are.
Nashit 客人的甜点里没有叉子
Nashit, there's not a fork in the mix out there.
现在 赶紧去叉那些女人
Now, get out there and fork those women.
别难为他
Take it easy on him.
我可不想他为我服务的时候
I don't want him to be all forked out
都累坏了
by the time he gets to me.
我要和Nashit在床上大战三百回合
I'm gonna have so much sex on my bed with Nashit
以至于到换新床单的地步
that I'm gonna need a new sheet.
你这年纪对他来说有点大了吧?
Aren't you too old for him?
嗯 但测试说我心理年龄只有十四岁
Yeah, but that test said mentally I'm 14,
所以我们完全能做
so we can totally do it.
我要去唐人街找人
Well, I'm off to Chinatown to have someone
做针灸了
put needles in me.
天啊 我大爱你的外套啊
Oh, my God. I love your coat.
你看起来美极了
You look gorgeous.
我是说 外套如此飘逸
I mean, the way it flows.
好吧 我看出来你是个马屁精了
Okay, so I can see you're a kiss-ass,
是这样的
so here's the thing.
作为我的准经理
As my quasi-manager,
或者随便你跟别人说的什么
or whatever nonsense you're telling people,
我要你告诉Max和Nashit别兴奋
I need you to tell Max and Nashit to cool it.
"糕潮"的员工之间不能勾搭
There are no hookups here at The High.
没问题 要是咱们对经理任命意见一致
Done, and we can stop saying quasi
那个"准"字就可以免了
if we're both on board with the manager thing.
我没看好
We're not.
"糕潮"的招牌是精致糕点
The High is about fine pastry,
而不是你们的淫秽私生活
not someone's sordid love life.
但作为讽刺性的反转 要是我女朋来了
And in an ironic twist, I need you to kick
我要你把她从这里
my girlfriend's hot ass out of here
弄出去
if she comes in.
这是一百块
Here's $100.
一百块啊
That's $100.
赶她这事儿没商量
Consider her hot ass out the door.
我们吵架了
We're in a fight.
她喝醉了 偷了我的黑卡
She got drunk, stole my Black Card,
在巴尼·格林格拉斯餐厅请了九十个人喝汤
and bought 90 people soup at Barney Greengrass,
关键是那里的汤根本不好喝
and the soup isn't even good there.
别误会我在拒绝你 因为我很需要钱
Do not take this as a no, because I want the money,
但你为什么不自己告诉她呢?
but why can't you just tell her yourself?
我不能亲口跟她说
I can't tell her myself.
她比我年轻 大家都知道
She's younger than me, and everyone knows
妈妈式的女人可不性感
the mommy thing just isn't sexy.
保证她吃点东西 并且安全到家
Make sure she eats something and gets home safe.
Caroline 我有个问题问你
Caroline, I have a question for you.
我该怎么处理女人们给我的纸条啊?
What do I do with the notes the women give me?
你收到纸条了?
You've gotten notes?
几张而已
Just a few.
女人们怎么这么饥渴?
How could women be this desperate?
Max 这张是你写的
Max, this one's from you.
几乎都是我写的
They're mostly all from me,
除了那张名片
except the business card.
我可不需要什么名片
I don't need no damn card
来告诉他我随时接客
to let him know I'm all business.
Max Joe刚跟我说"糕潮"店里不能勾搭
Max, Joe just told me there are no hookups at The High,
而从你这细节生动的画来看
and judging from this very detailed picture you drew,
你一门心思只想勾搭啊
that's exactly what you're planning.
哦 我想的还多着呢 但是纸不够用了
Oh, I was planning more. I just ran out of paper.
我们不能丢了这份工作
We can't lose these jobs.
我有两张百元大钞 而且就差这么一点
I have two $100 bills, and I'm this close
就能申请亚马逊金牌会员了
to pulling the trigger on an Amazon Prime account.
亚马逊金牌服务?
Amazon Prime?
你真是被权利冲昏头脑了
You have been driven mad with power.
新鲜的千层酥饼
Fresh, flakey pastry.
说起小薄饼
And speaking of flakes,
Joe的古怪女朋友在那边
there's Joe's flakey girlfriend.
谁帮我把椅子从外套上拿下来?
Can someone help me get my chair off my coat?
她怎么进来的?
How did she get in here?
估计是坐毒品云飘进来的
Probably floated in on a cloud of Valium.
该行动了 也就是她得离开
It's go time, as in she's got to go.
你还不如去搬运失事列车呢
You have a better chance moving an actual train wreck,
但祝你好运
but good luck.
- Allie 嗨 你...  - 嘘
- Allie, hi, you...  - Shh.
Allie 嗨
Allie, hi.
- 你得...  - 抱歉
- You need...  - Sorry.
但我还宿醉着呢 而且头疼
But I am hungover, and I have a headache.
能给我杯拿铁配大麻么?
Could I get a latte with a side of weed?
不行 因为这里不是阿姆斯特丹
No, because this isn't Amsterdam
或者比尔·马赫的家
or Bill Maher's house.
你得走了
Now, you need to leave.
你知道Joe不想你进来
You know Joe doesn't want you in here.
我不走
Well, I'm not leaving.
我的腿动不了
My legs won't move
因为肌肉松弛剂刚开始起效
because my muscle relaxers just kicked in.
John 能帮我个忙吗?
John, can you do me a favor?
送Allie出去
Walk Allie outside,
也就是说 把她抬起来
and by that, I mean pick her up
扛到外面去
and carry her outside.
我上的是糕点学校
I went to pastry school.
我不是怪物史莱克
I'm not Shrek.
当然不是 你更像维奥娜公主
Of course not. You're much more Fiona.
妹子 说得好
Girl, that's good.
我本想说驴子的 因为我屁股很翘
I was gonna say the donkey, 'cause I have a fine ass.
啊哦 好吧
Okay, fine.
司机 停两站 巴尼斯精品店和冰冻酸奶店
Driver, two stops. Barney's and Fro-Yo.
Earl 我们又迟到了 你帮我们照应着没？
Earl, we're late again. Did you keep us alive?
Max 我都自身难保了
Max, I can barely keep myself alive.
今天上午 我不得不把手指插到
This morning, I had to jump-start my heart
插座里给心脏起搏
by putting my finger in the socket
猫捉老鼠里的姿势
Tom and Jerry style.
哦 你好
Oh, hello.
姑娘们 你们今天做什么了?
So what did you girls do today?
自昨晚起 我就没见过你们了
I haven't seen you since right here last night.
哦 是吗 Han?
Oh, really, Han?
因为我发誓我看见你潜伏在
'Cause I swear I saw you lurking around
"糕潮"外面
outside The High.
要么是你
It was either you,
要么是皮卡丘造访纽约了
or Pikachu is visiting New York.
这话有点伤到我了
That one barely grazed me,
因为我是韩国人
because I'm Korean,
而皮卡丘是日本的
and Pikachu is Japanese.
你根本不了解"神奇宝贝"
You don't know anything about Pokemon.
Han 你也许不是日本人
Han, you may not be Japanese,
但我敢说你在未来
but in the future, you're definitely
肯定会被日本人日了
gonna be poked by a Mon.
而那个人就是你
And it was you.
不 不是
No, it was not.
- 是 就是  - 不是
- Yeah, it was.  - Wasn't.
- 是  - 不是
- Was.  - Wasn't.
- 不是  - 是... 不是
- Wasn't.  - Was... wasn't.
英语是我的第二语言
English is my second language.
承认吧 你是嫉妒
Admit it, you're jealous
我们把时间都花在另一间餐厅了
we're spending time with another restaurant.
我不是嫉妒
I am not jealous.
- 是  - 不是
- Are so.  - Am not.
- 不是  - 是... 不是
- Am not.  - Are so... not.
天啊!
Oh, my God!
Caroline 你在搞什么鬼?
Caroline, what the hell are you doing?
我在闻一张百元纸币
I'm smelling a $100 bill.
这是从我的另一间餐厅拿的
It's from my other restaurant.
它能给我买很多好东西
It buys me nice things.
嫉妒吗?
Jealous?
我在你一无所有的时候 收留了你
I took you in when you had no one.
嗨 能帮我个忙吗?
Hi, can you help me?
我找Max
I'm looking for Max.
有事吗 你好 现在做基佬还来得及吗
Why, hello. Is it too late to be gay?
Nashit 你怎么来了?
Nashit?
天啊 他在太平间的灯光下
Oh, my God, he even looks good here
还是那么好看
in morgue light.
我们绝对要上床
We are so doing it.
Caroline 你把手机落在餐厅的
Caroline, you left your phone on the table
桌子上了
at the restaurant.
我承认 我以此为借口
I confess, I used it as an excuse
来见Max
to come and see Max.
这不是我的 这是Joe的女朋友的
This isn't mine. It's Joe's girlfriend's.
我没有"苹果6"
I don't have an iPhone 6.
我有"苹果"病
I have an iPhone sick.
来做吧
D-O-I-N-G it!
Max Nashit怎么会在这儿?
Max, why is Nashit here?
因为是上帝欠我的
Because God owes me.
你不能真的喜欢上他
You can't seriously be into him.
他看起来像是男孩乐队的成员
He looks like someone in a boy band.
是的 然后他就可以直插无误...
Yeah, and he's going one direction...
下面
Down there.
但要是你跟他睡了
But if you sleep with him,
Nashit会遇到麻烦的
then Nashit is gonna hit the fan.
你怎么知道你喜欢他?
How do you know you even like him?
你知道我喜欢什么吗? 就是我们在嘿咻
You know what I like? That we're doing it.
嘿 各位亲!
Hey, everybody!
我刚刚被一辆的士撞了
I just got hit by a cab,
不过我有兴致吃蟹腿呢
and, boy, am I in the mood for crab legs.
关于你的这件事 宝贝...
The thing about you, baby...
每个晚上的每次重击后
you bounce back from a good pounding
你都恢复得很快
every single night.
等等
Wait a minute.
那是我的位置
That's my booth.
哦 很高兴见到你
Oh, it's lovely to meet you.
什么?
What?
那究竟是什么口音?
What the hell kind of accent is that?
我来自爱尔兰
I'm from Ireland.
什么?
What?
Max 你不能做
Max, you are not doing it.
- 做  - 不做
- Are.  - Not.
- 不做  - 拜托 我是沃顿商学院出来的
- Not.  - Please, I went to Wharton.
听着 我们做的时候 应该去你家
Look, we should go to your place when we do it
这样 Caroline就不会在我们做的过程中出现
so that Caroline won't be there while we're doing it.
很好 可我两天前才刚来美国
Lovely, but I just came to America two days ago.
我没地方可去
I have no place to go.
事实上 我一直睡在那张脏椅子上
In fact, I've been sleeping on that dirty chair
Joe说过的那张
Joe spoke of.
什么?
What?
他在唱歌吗?
Is he singing?
天啊
Oh, my God.
他又迷人又无家可归?
He's gorgeous and homeless?
那就是你的梦中情人啊
That's your dream guy.
我们绝对要嘿咻
We are so doing it!
呃 这不可能
Ugh, this is impossible.
我感觉自己穿上了珍藏版的奥斯卡礼服
I feel like I'm putting an Oscar dress on Precious.
我正在给Nashit铺沙发
I'm making up the couch for Nashit.
你真是太好了
That is so nice of you.
在我们做爱后 他需要有个地方休息
He's gonna need a place to crash after we have sex.
不 我们不讨论这个
No, that's off the table.
我不敢相信 你邀请他留在这里
I can't believe you invited him to stay here.
我也不敢相信 你今晚
And I can't believe you refused
拒绝睡在星巴克 为我们腾出私人空间
to sleep at Starbucks tonight to give us some privacy.
你简直就是诺拉·琼斯
I mean, you like Nora Jones.
Max的菜
Max likey.
- Max 听着  - 不 你听着
- Max, listen.  - No, you listen.
我买不起糖 所以我只能舔他
I can't afford candy, so he has got to be it.
谢谢你的浴室
Thanks for the shower.
天啊 他的肌肉一直蔓延到他的鸡鸡
Oh, no, his muscles point to his penis.
Max 别再敲了
Max, stop with the banging.
我不会在你还"性"致勃勃时 让你出来的
I'm not letting you out while you're still in heat.
不是我
It's not me.
我正在想杀你的方法!
I'm making a list of ways to kill you!
我感觉自己成了个麻烦
I feel like I'm being a bother,
而且感觉自己睡在烟斗上
and I think I'm sleeping on a bong.
开门
Open up.
我知道里面在做什么
I know what's going on in there.
天啊
Oh, my God.
是Joe
That's Joe.
她一定已经发现 你和Max在约炮了
She must've found out about you and Max hooking up.
哦 不
Oh, no.
Max Joe在这里
Max, Joe is here.
你要像你以前那样
You need to do that thing you do
把走廊里的人吓跑
to scare people out of the hallway.
怎么做 装看门狗
What do we think, guard dog
还是持着枪 但视力不好的
or little old lady with poor eyesight
老婆婆?
and loaded gun?
得 我走了
Fine, I'm going.
这就是我不肯离开曼哈顿的原因
This is why I never leave Manhattan.
嘿 你要进姑娘们的房间吗?
Hey, you need to get in the girls' apartment?
我有钥匙
I have a key.
我在大包里找找
Find it here in my big bag.
我知道它就在里面
I know it's in here somewhere.
我找到唇膏
Well, I got the lip balm.
还有... 看啊 我找到本圣经
I got... Oh, look, I got the Holy Bible.
还有...
I got...
看啊 这是直播电视的遥控机
Oh, look. Oh, the DirecTV remote.
天啊 我的雌性激素没了
Oh, my God, I'm losing estrogen.
Max 你和Nashit躲到你房间去
Max, you and Nashit go hide in your room,
但不准啪啪啪
but no sex.
你听她说了 不准啪啪啪
You heard her, no sex,
所以除此之外都要 我是说除此外的一切
so everything but, and I mean everything,
我是说都要
and I mean but.
找到了 它在...
Oh, here it is. It's right...
原来一直放在冷切肠下面啊
It was right under the cold cuts the whole time.
嗨Caroline
Caroline.
嗨 Joe
Hey. Hi, Joe.
哦!
Oh!
耶
Yeah.
哈!
Ha!
原来你剪短发是因为这原因
Yeah, the shorter hair makes sense now.
好啊
Yeah.
不错嘛 Caroline
Good for you, Caroline.
我希望你会喜欢又臭又长的故事
I hope you like long, boring stories.
好了 Allie在哪? 我知道她在这
Okay, where's Allie? I know she's here.
我在她手机里装了个监视应用
I put a spy app on her phone,
虽然不光彩 但我是个嫉妒心很强的女人
and I'm not proud of it, but I'm a jealous woman.
她的手机啊 在我这
Oh, her phone. I have it.
她今天被我赶出去时 把它落在"糕潮"了
She left it at The High when I threw her ass out today
遵从你的指示哦
per your instructions.
我真不知道我为什么会
I don't know how I thought this thing
从一开始就认为我们会合适
was gonna work out to begin with.
我们在科切拉音乐节遇见的
We met at Coachella.
当时我们都迷上了一个性感的
We were both on Molly, this intensely hot
菲律宾女孩
Filipino girl.
- 嘘  - 我听见啪啪啪的声音
- Shh, shh.  - I'm hearing sexual sounds.
还有一丝偷偷摸摸的羞愧 是从卧室传来的
And hints of secret shame coming from the bedroom.
- Allie就在这  - 不 这没人
- Allie is here.  - No, no one's here.
那只是我们的白噪声机
That's just our white noise machine.
我吓呆了 你都不是她的菜
I'm shocked. You're not even her type.
你的嘴唇像是用圆珠笔画的
Your lips are like two flair-pen marks.
真性感
That's hot.
不要开除Nashit!
Please don't fire Nashit!
戴苏斯博士的帽子是我的主意
The Dr. Seuss hats were my idea.
戴苏斯博士 美国最受欢迎的儿童作家
戴苏斯博士所著的书
我们在玩"在老爸身上跳来跳去"
We were playing Hop on Pop.
我是老爸
I was Pop.
我都不知道里面有个男的
I didn't even know there was a boy in there.
我只看见了你
I only saw you.
好吧 鉴于"糕潮"不允许员工谈恋爱
Okay, since there are no hookups at The High,
如果你不立刻跟他断交
if you don't stop sleeping with him immediately,
我的新经理...
my new manager...
Caroline就要把他那漂亮的屁屁
Caroline here is gonna have to kick
赶回马路边去
his beautiful butt to the curb.
但人家还在做啊!
But I was mid-doing-it!
亲爱的 这里真的有股怪味
Honey, there's a real funky smell in here.
我得离开这
I got to get out of here.
另外 你就住这?
PS, this is where you live?
再收下这100刀吧
Take another $100.
Earl  嗨
Earl, hi.
Max现在的心情怎么样
What kind of mood is Max in?
不错啊
Pretty good.
按她的标准 就是没有醉
On the Max scale, she's below slightly drunk
但是想把客人赶跑
but above punching a customer out.
这就好
Oh, good.
我还担心她会对我发火
I was worried she'd be mad at me
因为我迫不得已赶走了他的男宠
'cause I had to get rid of her boy toy.
Caroline 我要是想听你讲故事
Caroline, I'd put my hearing aids back in
就会把助听器戴上
if I wanted to hear a story.
猜猜我包里给你准备了什么
Guess what I have for you in my purse.
我上周问你要的卫生棉条?
The tampon I asked for last week?
不对 我还是要为那事道歉
No, and again, so sorry about that.
真的忘掉了
Really dropped that ball.
粘毛虫软糖
Gummy worms.
我确实赶走了你的甜心
Yes, I took away your man candy,
但我给你带了你爱的畅销糖果
but I got you these, the hot ones that you like
就是那家有个打喷嚏的保安的高级糖果店
from the good candy store with the sneeze guards.
高级货
Fancy.
还有别担心Nashit
And don't worry about Nashit.
我给他找了份新工作
I got him another job.
毛毛虫!
Hot worm!
干净的酒杯来了
Clean glasses coming through.
挂着好看
Nice rack.
现在我知道为什么男人喜欢跟我说这个
Now I know why guys like saying that to me.
他在这
There he is!
新员工在这
There's the new employee.
Han 我不敢相信你会因为Max求你
Han, I can't believe you would hire someone
而雇一个新员工
just 'cause Max asked you to.
这事跟你和Max没关系
This has nothing to do with Max or you.
这孩子跟我说了一句
The boy here said something to me
你俩永远理解不了的东西
that you two couldn't understand.
是什么 老板?
What's that, sir?
我是个勤劳肯干的员工?
That I was a hard worker?
对! 就是这个
That's it! Yes!
天降甘露啊
Manna from heaven.
我居然招到个肯干活的员工
I actually have an employee who works.
嫉妒吗?
Jealous?
这个活 我干得了
Now, this job, I can do.
我从小到大 有5个兄弟姐妹
You know, growing up, I had five brothers and sisters,
因为我长得最难看
and since I was the least attractive,
全部的盘子都得我洗
I had to clean all the dishes.
洗盘室见 Nashit
Meet you in the dish room, Nashit.
Max 你在干嘛
Max, what are you doing?
也许"糕潮"不允许员工勾搭
There may not be hookups at The High,
但是在这低谷可以尽情放纵
but there are hookups here at our lowest low,
还有我们就是要做
and we are doing it.
Caroline的最爱
Caroline likey.